(Leonard:)You still got the part.
That's a huge accomplishment.
(Penny:)But this was supposed
to be my break, okay?
(Penny:)People were gonna
see me in this show
(Penny:)and it was gonna
lead to bigger things.
(Penny:)More auditions, more parts.
Now none of that's gonna happen.
Honey, you only had three lines.
That wasn't gonna happen anyway.
(Penny:)Unbelievable.
-Oh, come on.
(Leonard:)-That's not what I meant.
-Then what did you mean?
I don't-- You know, words don't
always have to mean things.
(Penny:)I think you meant
that you don't believe in me.
Nope. Uh-uh. I might not
know what I meant,
(Leonard:)but I know that
I didn't mean that.
(Leonard:)Not this guy. Oh, no way.
(Penny:)I want you, right now, to give me
your 100 percent honest opinion.
(Penny:)Do you think I have what it takes
to really make it as an actress?
(Leonard:)-Yes.
-So you think I'll be on TV
(Penny:)and in movies and win awards.
(Leonard:)-Honestly?
-Yes, honestly.
(Penny:)-I don't.
-How could you say that?
(Leonard:)I don't know-- I got all confused
when you said "honestly."